<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ZooZooApp</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Shendy Krisyohanda</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">NIM : 2010817310006</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="setting">Change Languages</string>

    <string name="home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="animals_title">Info Animal</string>
    <string name="african_title">African Animals</string>
    <string name="asian_title">Asian Animals</string>
    <string name="european_title">European Animals</string>
    <string name="north_american_title">North American Animals</string>

    <string name="hello_home_fragment">Welcome to ZooZooApp</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- African Animals -->

    <!-- Animals Name   -->
    <string name="aardvark_name">Aardvark</string>
    <string name="addax_name">Addax</string>
    <string name="african_civet_name">African Civet</string>
    <string name="hippopotamus_name">Hippopotamus</string>
    <string name="xerus_name">Xerus</string>

    <!-- Animals Diet   -->
    <string name="aardvark_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="addax_diet">Herbivore</string>
    <string name="african_civet_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="hippopotamus_diet">Herbivore</string>
    <string name="xerus_diet">Omnivore</string>

    <!-- Animals Lifespan   -->
    <string name="aardvark_lifespan">23 years</string>
    <string name="addax_lifespan">19-25 years</string>
    <string name="african_civet_lifespan">15-20 years</string>
    <string name="hippopotamus_lifespan">40-50 years</string>
    <string name="xerus_lifespan">11.5 years</string>

    <!-- Animals weight  -->
    <string name="aardvark_weight">60kg-80kg</string>
    <string name="addax_weight">Unknown</string>
    <string name="african_civet_weight">1.4kg-4.5kg</string>
    <string name="hippopotamus_weight">1tonne-4.5tonnes</string>
    <string name="xerus_weight">Unknown</string>

    <!-- Animals length   -->
    <string name="aardvark_length">3.4ft-7.3ft</string>
    <string name="addax_length">47 to 51 inches</string>
    <string name="african_civet_length">17in-28in</string>
    <string name="hippopotamus_length">6.5ft-16.5ft</string>
    <string name="xerus_length">17in-18in</string>

    <!-- Asian Animals -->

    <!-- Animals Name   -->
    <string name="ape_name">Ape</string>
    <string name="dwarf_hamster_name">Dwarf Hamster</string>
    <string name="fire_eel_name">Fire Eel</string>
    <string name="japanese_macaque_name">Japanese Macaque</string>
    <string name="siberian_tiger_name">Siberian Tiger</string>

    <!-- Animals Diet   -->
    <string name="ape_diet">Herbivore</string>
    <string name="dwarf_hamster_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="fire_eel_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="japanese_macaque_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="siberian_tiger_diet">Carnivore</string>

    <!-- Animals Lifespan   -->
    <string name="ape_lifespan">50 years</string>
    <string name="dwarf_hamster_lifespan">2-3 years</string>
    <string name="fire_eel_lifespan">10-20 years</string>
    <string name="japanese_macaque_lifespan">25-32 years</string>
    <string name="siberian_tiger_lifespan">18-25 years</string>

    <!-- Animals weight  -->
    <string name="ape_weight">Varies</string>
    <string name="dwarf_hamster_weight">0.71 – 0.88 ounces</string>
    <string name="fire_eel_weight">Unknown</string>
    <string name="japanese_macaque_weight">5kg - 14kg</string>
    <string name="siberian_tiger_weight">100kg - 350kg</string>

    <!-- Animals length   -->
    <string name="ape_length">Varies</string>
    <string name="dwarf_hamster_length">5.5 – 10.5 cm</string>
    <string name="fire_eel_length">20 - 40 inches</string>
    <string name="japanese_macaque_length">80cm - 95cm</string>
    <string name="siberian_tiger_length">Unknown</string>

    <!-- European Animals -->

    <!-- Animals Name   -->
    <string name="barn_owl_name">Barn Owl</string>
    <string name="chamois_name">Chamois</string>
    <string name="grouse_name">Grouse Bird</string>
    <string name="stag_beetle_name">Stag Beetle</string>
    <string name="woodlouse_spider_name">Woodlouse Spider</string>

    <!-- Animals Diet   -->
    <string name="barn_owl_diet">Carnivore</string>
    <string name="chamois_diet">Herbivore</string>
    <string name="grouse_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="stag_beetle_diet">Herbivore</string>
    <string name="woodlouse_spider_diet">Carnivore</string>

    <!-- Animals Lifespan   -->
    <string name="barn_owl_lifespan">5 - 10 years</string>
    <string name="chamois_lifespan">18 - 22 years</string>
    <string name="grouse_lifespan">1 - 10 years</string>
    <string name="stag_beetle_lifespan">3-7 years</string>
    <string name="woodlouse_spider_lifespan">Unknown</string>

    <!-- Animals weight  -->
    <string name="barn_owl_weight">300g - 550g</string>
    <string name="chamois_weight">50kg - 55kg</string>
    <string name="grouse_weight">0.3kg - 6.5kg</string>
    <string name="stag_beetle_weight">Up to 0.5 grams</string>
    <string name="woodlouse_spider_weight">Unknown</string>

    <!-- Animals length   -->
    <string name="barn_owl_length">25cm - 45cm</string>
    <string name="chamois_length">75cm - 80cm</string>
    <string name="grouse_length">31cm - 95cm</string>
    <string name="stag_beetle_length">1cm – 12.3cm</string>
    <string name="woodlouse_spider_length">0.3inchi-0.5inchi</string>

    <!-- North American Animals -->

    <!-- Animals Name   -->
    <string name="alaskan_husky_name">Alaskan Husky</string>
    <string name="bald_eagle_name">Bald Eagle</string>
    <string name="deer_tick_name">Deer Tick</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_monk_seal_name">Hawaiian Monk Seal</string>
    <string name="pileated_woodpecker_name">Pileated Woodpecker</string>

    <!-- Animals Diet   -->
    <string name="alaskan_husky_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="bald_eagle_diet">Carnivore</string>
    <string name="deer_tick_diet">Omnivore</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_monk_seal_diet">Carnivore</string>
    <string name="pileated_woodpecker_diet">Omnivore</string>

    <!-- Animals Lifespan   -->
    <string name="alaskan_husky_lifespan">10 – 12 years</string>
    <string name="bald_eagle_lifespan">15-20 years</string>
    <string name="deer_tick_lifespan">2 years</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_monk_seal_lifespan">30 years</string>
    <string name="pileated_woodpecker_lifespan">12 years</string>

    <!-- Animals weight  -->
    <string name="alaskan_husky_weight">65 lbs</string>
    <string name="bald_eagle_weight">6.6-14lbs</string>
    <string name="deer_tick_weight">Unknown</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_monk_seal_weight">Unknown</string>
    <string name="pileated_woodpecker_weight">8.8 to 12.3 ounces</string>

    <!-- Animals length   -->
    <string name="alaskan_husky_length">Unknown</string>
    <string name="bald_eagle_length">28-38 inches</string>
    <string name="deer_tick_length">2-6 mm</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_monk_seal_length">7-8 feet</string>
    <string name="pileated_woodpecker_length">16 to 19 inches</string>

    <string name="detail_animals_name">detail\'s name</string>
    <string name="detail_scientific_name_label">Scientific Name :</string>
    <string name="detail_diet_label">Diet :</string>
    <string name="detail_lifespan_label">Lifespan :</string>
    <string name="detail_weight_label">Weight :</string>
    <string name="detail_lenght_label">Lenght :</string>
    <string name="detail_more_label">Tap the image to know more!</string>

    <string name="info1">
        Aardvarks are small pig-like mammals that are found inhabiting a wide range of different habitats
        throughout Africa, south of the Sahara. They are mostly solitary and spend their days sleeping in
        underground burrows to protect them from the heat of the African sun, emerging in the cooler evening
        to search for food. Their name originates from the Afrikaans language in South Africa and means Earth Pig,
        due to their long snout and pig-like body. Aardvarks are unique among animals as they are the only
        surviving species in their animal family. Until recently it was widely believed that they were most
        closely related to other insectivores such as armadillos and pangolins but this is not the case with
        their closest living relatives actually thought to be elephants.
    </string>
    <string name="info2">
        This beautiful antelope, also called the screwhorn or white antelope once ranged over the Sahara Desert.
        Now it is on the edge of extinction due to poaching, climate change, overhunting, and habitat destruction.
        Fortunately, efforts are being made to return its wild population to healthy numbers.
    </string>
    <string name="info3">
        The African Civet is a large species of Civet found across sub-Saharan Africa. The African Civet is the
        only remaining member in its genetic group and is considered to be the largest Civet-like animal on the
        African continent. Despite their cat-like appearance and behaviours, the African Civets are not felines
        at all but are in fact, more closely related to other small carnivores including Weasels and Mongooses.
        The African Civet is most well known for the musk that it secretes to mark its territory (called Civetone),
        which has been used in the manufacturing of perfumes for centuries, and its striking black and white markings,
        make the African Civet one of the easiest Civet species to identify.
    </string>
    <string name="info4">
        The Hippopotamus is a large semi-aquatic mammal that is found wallowing in the rivers and lakes across sub-Saharan
        Africa. Despite its appearance, the Hippopotamus is an animal that is actually thought to be most closely related
        to Whales as the two are thought to have had a common ancestor that existed roughly 54 million years ago.
        Also known as the Common Hippopotamus, it is one of two Hippo species that are found on the African continent
        with the other being the solitary and forest-dwelling Pygmy Hippopotamus which is only found in western Africa
        and is now Critically Endangered. Although the Common Hippopotamus remains an abundant and widespread animal
        throughout its current range, numbers are reportedly declining due to both hunting and habitat loss.
    </string>
    <string name="info5">
        Xerus erythropus which is commonly known as African ground squirrel and is native to Africa.
        They have coarse and short hair and are known to be social animals. They can survive in captivity for about 11.5 years.
        The males and females live in their separate groups and come together to mate after which the babies live with their mothers in the group of females.
        The Xerus has four subspecies – cape ground squirrel, striped ground squirrel, mountain ground squirrel, and unstriped ground squirrel.
        These animals are diurnal and are usually known to be herbivores in nature and usually eat nuts, roots, and seeds. However,
        sometimes they also eat eggs and other small animals.
    </string>
    <string name="info6">
        Apes are part of the superfamily of primates, the Hominoidea. The Hominoidea encompasses a variety of species called
        “lesser apes” and “great apes.” These include the gorilla, orangutan, chimpanzee, bonobo and humans(!).
        There are other primates whose common name may include “ape,” but those species are not primates.
        Most primates are skilled climbers, especially when it comes to trees. They are omnivorous with a primary diet of
        vegetation. Foods include grass seeds, fruit, the rare partaking of meat or invertebrates. Scavenged or hunted,
        they consume pretty much anything available that’s easily ingested.
        Primates are native to Asia and Africa. Humans and species of great apes have startling similarities.
        Yet, at the same time, the gap in differences is huge when you compare the psychological, cultural, emotional, and spiritual aspects of each species.
        Every species has its own language, symbols, communication techniques and unique governance systems. But there’s no denying that human versions are
        far more complex. Technologies, scientific advancement, self-awareness and even religion put humans in a category outside of standard primates.
    </string>
    <string name="info7">
        A dwarf hamster is a group of several subspecies, specifically dealing with hamsters that are smaller than four inches long.
        They often have a lifespan of two to three years, though some live less than this. They are incredibly smart, and some subspecies
        hibernate through the winter months underground. If you want to take a little extra time with this furry pet, you may even learn
        how to train them to do different tricks.
    </string>
    <string name="info8">
        Called an eel for its long thin appearance, a Fire Eel actually isn’t a true eel at all.
        In fact, it is one of a species of elongated freshwater fish with pointy snouts known as spiny eels.
        These fish are popular aquarium pets because of their unusual color and size. These nocturnal,
        bottom-dwelling fish have long lives, both in the wild and as pets. Their price varies wildly depending on their size,
        from small to jumbo, so they can cost as little as $20 or have a price tag as high as a few hundred dollars.
        Though they rarely bite, they can be a bit dangerous due to their spines and toxins, and the way they thrash around when captured.
    </string>
    <string name="info9">
        The Japanese Macaque is a medium sized Monkey found in a variety of different habitats throughout Japan.
        The Japanese Macaque is also known as the Snow Monkey as they are often found living in colder regions of
        the country where heavy snowfall is common during the winter. They are the world’s most northern living
        Monkey species and have adapted incredibly to their surroundings and changing seasons. There are two different
        subspecies of Japanese Macaque, one which is found across northern and mainland Japan, and the other is restricted
        to one of the country’s southern islands. The two differ very slightly in size and appearance.
    </string>
    <string name="info10">
        The Siberian tiger is one of the fiercest predators in the world.
        With its immense size and powerful body, the Siberian tiger prowls the dense forests of Eastern
        Asia in search of prey. Specially adapted for the frigid climate in which it resides,
        it is a sophisticated predator capable of taking down almost any other animal, no matter its size.
        But because of the value placed on its luxurious fur and the supposed medicinal properties of its
        parts, the animal is under constant threat of extinction from human activity.
        Meticulous conservation efforts and protection from local governments will be required to bolster current population numbers.
    </string>

    <string name="info11">
        Barn owls are the most well-known member family of owls known for their stark white faces and haunting calls.
        They are extremely widespread, one of the most widespread bird species on earth.
        Barn owls keep the rodent population in check wherever they live by preying on rats and mice primarily.
        In many cultures, they are seen as harbingers of death or symbolize the afterlife.
    </string>
    <string name="info12">
        The chamois is a small, hoofed animal that is a goat antelope species.
        It is native to Asia Minor and the Eastern, Central, and Western European
        mountains at moderately high altitudes, and it was introduced to New Zealand.
        The pronunciation of its name resembles that of the French, while the pronunciation
        for its name as leather is based on “chamy” or “shammy”. Some subspecies of this bovid
        are having protection under the EU’s European Habitat Directive.
    </string>
    <string name="info13">
        Grouse are medium sized, stocky birds that live in the Northern Hemisphere.
        Their feathers closely resemble their habitat. This plumage provides them with camouflage and helps them survive.
        Grouse are birds that are closely related to chickens, turkeys and pheasants. About eight million of these upland
        game birds are hunted each year for food or sport in their grassy and forested habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="info14">
        The stag beetle is a family of large, hard-shelled, flying insects whose distinguishing trait is
        the ability to consume rotting wood as a larva. The name of this insect is derived from the giant
        mandibles on the male, which resemble the stags of a deer in the way they curve and branch.
        Their numbers appear to be declining in some parts of their range due to the loss of habitats and food sources.
    </string>
    <string name="info15">
        The Woodlouse spider is found throughout the world.
        They live in Australia, Asia, Europe, North America, South America, and Africa.
        This spider is named for the woodlice it hunts in its habitat.
        These spiders don’t make a web. Instead, they capture prey with their fangs, then deliver a dose of venom.
        The lifespan of this spider is two to five years.
    </string>
    <string name="info16">
        The Alaskan Husky is an athletic working dog that arose from a cross between several similar yet distinctive breeds.
        Genetically, it’s a close relative of the Alaskan Malamute and the Siberian Husky. It was later crossed with a few
        European breeds, including German pointers and the Saluki. Some of these animals even have some recent wolf heritage.
        Capable of enduring harsh climates of the frigid north, the Alaskan Huskies are excellent sled dogs and companions that
        belong to the spitz group. The spitz dogs are characterized by thick white fur, pointed ears, long muzzles, and curled
        tails. However, because there isn’t a set breed standard, the Alaskan Husky can come in many different physical permutations
        and characteristics. They’re bred for speed and endurance, not for looks. As a result, they need to have an efficient gait,
        a warm double coat, and webbed feet that act as snowshoes. It’s also covered with some mixture of white, black, gray, brown, and even red fur.
    </string>
    <string name="info17">
        An endearing symbol of strength and power, the bald eagle is one of the most popular animals in all of North America.
        It soars majestically in the air, enthralling bird watchers and enthusiasts alike. While it was once on the brink of extinction,
        today it has recovered sufficiently to represent an astonishing conservation success story.
    </string>
    <string name="info18">
        Out of all the ticks native to North America, the deer tick is one of the most problematic.
        Ticks have been around for a very long time, over 100 million years. Today, there are more than 900 distinct species of ticks living
        on every continent (even Antarctica). Around 700 species are ‘hard-bodied’ ticks of the Ixodidae family.
        The deer tick is one of these hard-bodied species.
        Deer ticks are capable of ingesting so much blood that they engorge up to six times their normal size.
        When they latch onto a victim, they actually secrete an anesthetizing substance that deadens any pain inflicted by the bite.
        Like vampires, ticks live solely on blood. But, unlike Dracula—they don’t kill their victims, though they may impart blood-borne diseases to them.
    </string>
    <string name="info19">
        The Hawaiian monk seal, called Ilioholoikauaua by island natives, lives mostly around the Northwestern Hawaiian Islands.
        It is the official state mammal of Hawaii and only one of two mammals native to this U.S. state. Like other seals,
        they are meat eaters that hunt in ocean waters. They sleep on beaches where they also enjoy basking in the sun. As of 2016,
        there are only about 1400 of these native seals remaining.
    </string>
    <string name="info20">
        The largest of the North American common woodpeckers, pileated woodpeckers are birds that are easy to recognize thanks
        to the distinctive red crests atop their heads. Found primarily across southern Canada, the eastern United States,
        the northern Rockies, and parts of the Pacific Coast, pileated woodpeckers are monogamous, non-migratory birds.
        They prefer to inhabit old-growth forests with plenty of dead, standing trees, and they are famous for leaving
        rectangular holes in trees while searching for their favorite food – carpenter ants. These birds are not endangered
        and have steadily increasing population numbers.
    </string>
</resources>